<page
	xmlns="http://www.rustleund.com/fighting-fantasy/page"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" 
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.rustleund.com/fighting-fantasy/page ../../page.xsd">
	<pagenumber>137</pagenumber>
	<pagetext>
		<html>
			<p>
				As you make your way towards the eastern face of the mountain, a black-cloaked creature two metres tall leaps out from behind the cover
				of a large rock to attack you! Its body is vaguely human in proportion, but its great, green, scaly head is reptilian and its arms end in
				four-fingered, clawed hands. Its yellow, slitted eyes are full of hatred and menace as it snarls and spits at you and foetid, 
				brown-yellow wisps of noxious gas drift out of its fanged mouth! One of the Night Dragon's Stalkers is upon you, and battling it will be
				difficult. During each Attack Round, whenever you have a lower Attack Strength than your enemy, you must <i>Test Your Skill</i>.
				If you ever fail the test, the Stalker breaths over you and its foul breath weakens you; you will have to subtract 2 points from your
				Attack Strength during the rest of this combat, and 1 point from your Attack Strength in the next combat you face.
			</p>
			<p>
				<table border="1">
					<tr>
						<td> </td><td>SKILL</td><td>STAMINA</td>
					</tr>
					<tr>
						<td>GREEN STALKER</td><td align="right">10</td><td align="right">10</td>
					</tr>
				</table>
			</p>
			<p>
				Click <a href="http://dobattle:0">here</a> to begin the battle.
			</p>
		</html>
	</pagetext>
	<battle id="0" canFlee="false">
		<enemies>
			<enemy name="GREEN STALKER" skill="10" stamina="10" />
		</enemies>
		<effects>
			<playerHit>
				<testFlag id="15">
					<successful />
					<unsuccessful>
						<testSkill>
							<successful />
							<unsuccessful>
								<setFlag id="15" />
								<addBattleMessage message="You failed the Skill test, the Stalker breathes over you and its foul breath weakens you&lt;br&gt;" />
								<adjustPlayerAttackStrength amount="-2" />
								<addBattleEffectsToCurrentBattle>
									<battleEffects>
										<endBattle>
											<adjustPlayerAttackStrength amount="2" />
											<addBattleEffectsForNextBattle>
												<battleEffects>
													<startBattle>
														<adjustPlayerAttackStrength amount="-1" />
													</startBattle>
													<endBattle>
														<adjustPlayerAttackStrength amount="1" />
													</endBattle>
												</battleEffects>
											</addBattleEffectsForNextBattle>
										</endBattle>
									</battleEffects>
								</addBattleEffectsToCurrentBattle>
							</unsuccessful>
						</testSkill>
					</unsuccessful>
				</testFlag>
			</playerHit>
			<endBattle>
				<displayText id="0" />
				<adjustScale type="nemesis" amount="1" />
			</endBattle>
		</effects>
	</battle>
	<text id="0">
		You slay the horror; its eyes gaze at you with a malign menace as it perishes, as if someone -- or some<i>thing</i> -- else was still looking
		at you. 1 is added to your Nemesis score. Now you can <a href="http://link:169">continue your search round this mountain</a> or
		<a href="http://link:78">return to the tunnel entrance you know of and enter there</a>. 
	</text>
</page>