<page
	xmlns="http://www.rustleund.com/fighting-fantasy/page"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" 
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.rustleund.com/fighting-fantasy/page ../../page.xsd">
	<pagenumber>212</pagenumber>
	<pagetext>
		<html>
			<p>
				After leaving Port Blacksand far behind, days of determined marching bring you to the
				small village of Marzail, just over half-way to Rentarn. You must eat three meals from
				your supply of Provisions during this time and add 6 to your Time Track. In Marzail, 
				there's an inn where you can <a href="http://domulti:0">stay and get hot food and a good 
				bed for the night</a>, if you pay 2 Gold Pieces (you will regain 4 STAMINA points for 
				this rest). Alternatively, you can <a href="http://domulti:1">sleep outdoors</a> for 
				free (but you regain no STAMINA points and you must eat another meal).
			</p>
		</html>
	</pagetext>
	<immediate>
		<adjustScale type="provisions" amount="-3" />
		<adjustScale type="time" amount="6" />
	</immediate>
	<multicommand id="0">
		<adjustScale type="gold" amount="-2" promptOnFail="true" />
		<adjustScale type="stamina" amount="4" />
		<displayText id="0" />
	</multicommand>
	<multicommand id="1">
		<mustEatMeal amount="1" />
		<displayText id="0" />
	</multicommand>
	<text id="0">
		<p>
			In the morning, you continue your footslog along the coast road, which continues along more 
			undulating terrain. As you get to the crest of one hill, you hear chanting below! Peering around
			from behind the cover of a boulder, you see a group of three grey-cloaked men walking slowly along
			the road in front of you; they are swinging small incense-burners and chanting as they go. To the
			east, you can see a plume of smoke rising from the edge of some pine woods. Will you:
			<ul>
				<li><a href="http://link:252">Approach the grey-cloaked men?</a></li>
				<li><a href="http://link:382">Make for the woodland?</a></li>
				<li><a href="http://link:275">Avoid both, detour westwards, then continue north?</a></li>
			</ul>
		</p>
	</text>
</page>