<page
	xmlns="http://www.rustleund.com/fighting-fantasy/page"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" 
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.rustleund.com/fighting-fantasy/page ../../page.xsd">
	<pagenumber>49</pagenumber>
	<pagetext>
		<html>
			<p>
				The Dragons are silent as you clamber down the steps and stand before them with your head bowed. The Gold Dragon speaks, his voice 
				booming in this vast auditorium. 'It is not often that Dragon Elders meet in this way, human. We only meet when a great danger
				threatens us all. We have to turn to a human for help against the waking menace we all face. You have been chosen.' The Gold
				Dragon pushes his huge, three-metre head in your direction; his eyes are red and rheumy with age, but they shine with expectation
				and vigour despite his untold years.
			</p>
			<p>
				The Silver Dragon speaks next. 'Our messenger told you of the Night Dragon?' You nod slowly. 'Then all you need to know is the 
				reason we have asked you to come before us. The Ancient was overcome before by human heroes. They had powerful magic with which
				to defeat him. We know where that magic may be found. There is a great sword, hidden in the desolate Mist Crypts south-west of 
				here. The entrance to them lies below a tall mountain with a streak of fool's gold near its peak. To the north-west lies magic
				armour, crafted by the greatest dwarven artisans of their age and lost when their clan disappeared from Titan. Slake Peak was
				their old fortress home. Far to the east and south can be found a magic shield, lost among the Jublez &#8212; the Frost Giants, a 
				much tougher race than most of their kind. All these artefacts have great power against the Ancient. An exceptional hero armed and
				protected with these could vanquish him, should he be encountered before his sleep is wholly ended. You may even prevail without
				all these things &#8212; though without at least two you would find it impossible to overcome the Night Dragon.' There is one obvious
				question left: where is the Ancient? Click <a href="http://link:309">here</a> to continue.
			</p>
		</html>
	</pagetext>
</page>